No living creature was harmed during
the production of this tv show.
Osman.
I will never kneel before you.
Here is the battlefield.
I will cut your face under the mask...
...in half!
Bala.
I'm with you, my Osman!
I'm here too, father.
Alps! For Baysungur! For our martyrs!
For our vengeance!
-Allah is the greatest!
-O Allah!
-Attack!
Come.
I will make you pay for
attempting to kill my daughter!
I'll kill you in front of your daughter's eyes.
Brother, your double swords
can't compete with my solo.
You admire my swords! Come on!
Come on!
Brother!
Brother? Cerkutay? Brother?
My brother...
What did you do, brother?
Well, brother... I became
worthy of my double swords.
Oh brother... Oh Cerkutay...
-Boran.
-Yes, brother?
Come closer.
You should know this.
Cerkutay never dies.
You know, my heart is on the
right. This can't kill me.
You madman!
Let's go.
-Let's stick our swords into their hearts.
-Here we go.
Watch out!
-Get me up.
-Come, brother.
Cerkutay. This will hurt. Come on.
It hurt!
You're good.
You envied my double swords
and now I'm left with only one!
Allah is the greatest!
-Thank you, son.
-Thank you, my Bey. Come on, alps!
Come on, brothers!
You masked devil! Show yourself.
Who are you?
Fatma.
Fatma... Get up, dear.
-Are you alright? All good?
-I'm fine, mother.
Stay back.
Come on, come on.
Here we go.
You'll pay for setting me
up with your life, Bayhan.
Father!
-Die!
-Saruca!
Saruca! My son!
-Saruca?
-My son.
-My son. -Lukas.
Lukas!
My son.
Alps!
This smoke is toxic! Draw back!
Alaaddin! Take care of Saruca!
-As you order, my Bey!
-Alps, this way!
My Bey, I'm curious.
You haven't told me why we're going to Sogut.
A storm broke out in Sogut. Osman got disgraced.
And you're still asking me why we're going?
Don't you get it, Sancar?
They broke Osman's unbreakable pride.
We're going there to see his disgrace.
Okay, my Bey.
Here is my order, Sancar.
In the honor of Osman's losing Sogut,
...we'll hold a great feast and
offer food to beys and people.
As you order, my Bey.
How could that happen?
How did they save Fatma from Akhisar?
I swear I'll kill everyone who made mistakes.
This way.
Sofia
Run! Run!
Yusuf, go ahead of them from the right side.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Alps!
-Bala, you all go that way.
-Be careful, my Bey.
Let's go!
Let them come. We will see.
Run! Run!
You vile dog!
You asked for this.
Osman Bey has sent us here but...
...the heathens aren't around here.
Alps, we're going to the left side.
Your death is here.
You can't run anywhere!
Attack!
We should go, commander.
Our soldiers can stop Osman.
My Bey, they are running off!
Yusuf is there! They can't go anywhere!
I will kill them!
Boran, Cerkutay. Follow him!
Neither Lukas nor that snake
can survive in the woods!
Run, commander. Save yourself.
Sofia.
Sofia, stop.
That's Karesi Bey. Karesi Bey!
Karesi Bey.
You said you would take Sogut from Osman.
Lukas?
What happened?
No time for this. Osman is after
us. We need to get out of here.
Give us your horses.
We have to go, Lukas.
Osman can be here any minute.
Is this the woman you mentioned?
Yes, it's me.
Why hide your face?
Help us.
Or get out of our way, Karesi Bey.
You can go.
But you can't survive in the woods without me.
And you can't beat Osman without us, Karesi Bey.
You either help us now...
...or lose your best ally.
-Get in the carriage.
-Sofia, come on. Come on.
You can never..
Saruca! Saruca! My son!
Open your eyes! Come on!
Open your eyes! -Alps! Hold the streets!
Ensure Sogut's safety, come on! Come on!
Saruca
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes, my son
Bayhan Bey! Bayhan Bey! What are you doing?
If you take that dagger out, we
cannot stop the bleeding. Don't!
What are we going to do?
-Let go! Don't touch it!
Press it on the wound.
Alright, I am doing it!
Saruca, breathe, Saruca!
Saruca, breathe!
-Alaeddin, how is he?
The poisonous smoke hurt his lungs, brother.
I cannot do anything here!
The medicines are in the tribe.
We need to go to the tribe! Come on!
Will you save my son, Alaeddin?
-Will you save him?
-He will be alright, God willing.. Alps!
Bring the cart here!
We will take Saruca to the tribe, come on!
Come on! Let's go!
-I will come with you.
We cannot know what these dastard dogs will do.
Come on! Hurry!
-Hang on, my son!
Hang on Saruca! Hang on my son!
Lower the stretcher quickly!
Hang on. -Help! Come on!
Come on! Bring it here!
Come on! Come on! Hang on!
Here!
Push
Come on! Come on Alps!
Come on Bayhan Bey! Hurry!
Hurry!
Come on!
I hear voices there... Come on.
My Bey...
What are you doing here?
We were waiting, my Bey.
We decided to hold the left
side since Lukas didn't come.
How?
I gave you a duty.
Did you do what you decided on your own?
My Bey...
The infidels ran away from where you were.
You cannot disobey the state.
Don't you do it again.
Is there a trace?
There is no trace of Lukas, my Bey.
We've also lost the trail
of that jackal named Hristo.
But we heard something
from a shepherd on the way.
A horse-drawn cart was heading north, they said.
What if it's Lukas, Osman?
We will find out, my Bala.
-We will find out. Aykurt!
-My Bey! -Bring the horses!
Yes my Bey.
We'll take a better road than
the forest. We'll go there faster.
Okay my Bey.
Hang on... Hang on... Come on! Saruca!
Hang on my son!
Saruca. My son..
Hang on..
Hang on my son... We are almost there!
My Allah, keep my son with me!
Saruca is strong Bayhan Bey
You'll see. He will recover.
Alaeddin, Alaeddin Bey, will my son live?
Pull yourself together, Bayhan Bey!
We will be strong first. Calm down!
Father...
Saruca!
Saruca! My son..
Hold it here. Press with your hand.
Do it firmly, Bayhan Bey...
-Father...
Saruca... -Come on Alaeddin
Hang on Saruca, we will
arrive in the tribe soon!
Father..
Saruca... Why did you do
this? Why did you do this, son?
Why did you risk your life for me?
Don't you say that...
...I am incompetent?
-What is the value of my life?
-Don't talk like that.
You are a piece of my heart!
I waited for so long to
hear this from you, father.
Even if I die, I won't feel sorry now.
Saruca.
Saruca!
Open your eyes! Saruca! My son!
Come on! Hang on my son!
Come on Alaeddin Bey! Hurry!
My Bey, Osman Bey!
Karesi Bey...
What are you doing in Sogut?
What are you doing here?
I heard that..
...you were in a difficult position.
You were going to give...
...Sogut to the infidels
for your daughter's life.
Even if you see me as your enemy...
...I came here to help you but...
...you handled it yourself.
What is it?
Are you going to protect us now?
Yes, yes.
When it's about children..
...I don't look for enmity.
I came here to find the
middle way between you...
...and the infidels who you say I work
with and to save your daughter's life.
But I see that..
..there is no need for that.
May you recover soon, my daughter Fatma Hatun.
Thank you Karesi Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
But we cannot know for sure.
Maybe you are trying to find the middle
way for those who you want to protect, huh?
Don't worry.
Today, you will hear
their screams in the forest.
I won't ask anyone to
spare the life of an infidel.
Just because we traded with
them, you think we are the same.
You are responsible for this, Osman.
You think of frontiers as a hunting ground...
...and us as the prey you chase.
But if we were united..
...if we did politics together...
...if we ruled the frontiers together...
...if we hunted the infidels together...
...would we need any
allies other than ourselves?
So you are talking about hunting them huh?
We are also hunting, Karesi Bey.
We are after a couple of jackals.
Open that door!
What is it?
Karesi Bey.
Osman Bey.
Stop there.
I came here for your daughter's life.
-Are you accusing me of hiding an infidel?
-Karesi Bey.
If there's nothing you are afraid of...
...why are you standing against me, huh?
Move.
Move Karesi Bey.
Open the door.
Open the door!
My Bey, Osman Bey is coming this way!
Lukas, get out, now!
We'll meet after Osman is gone. Come on!
Our intentions are good, but...
What will happen to your disrespect...
...and ungratefulness Osman?
You want to stay enemies. What a pity.
As long as you step on my land without my
permission, this is how you will be treated.
Leave now.
Okay Osman Bey.
Okay.
Saruca, my son! Hang on! My son!
They are coming... They
won't be able to survive here.
Go ahead and inform the doctors.
Have them prepare everything.
-Yes my Bey.
Hang on, my son!
Ambush!
I will take my son's revenge!
You stay there!
I will deal with those dogs alone.
Stay with your son, Bayhan Bey!
Oh Allah! -Go!
Convey my greetings to those in hell.
Tell them you failed as well!
Father...
He cannot breathe!
Saruca is not alright, brother! We need to go!
You go! Go!
Come on Bayhan Bey! Come on!
Come on! We don't have time! He is bleeding!
Come on Alps! Come on!
Come at me!
Alps!
Go ahead and secure the area!
He is coming.
You got out of the carriage
just in time. If you hadn't...
...we would have fought with Osman.
You will get something in
return for this favor, Karesi Bey.
Of course I will.
You would never help us if you wouldn't
get anything from this anyway, Karesi Bey.
Don't boast for no reason.
You're a smart Hatun(Woman).
We will do so many things with you.
But I want to see the faces
of those I will work with.
Now tell me. Who are you?
Take it off..
Let me see your face.
My name is Sofia.
You will have to pay the
price of seeing my face.
Karesi Bey.
They know we'll take Sogut and
that they won’t get out of this forest.
They must have found a hole to hide, my Bey.
They left our lands.
How?
They left our lands with the help of Karesi Bey!
Here..
The tracks come this way.
The intensity of the tracks...
...increases in this area.
Clearly...
..he let someone in here.
We saw it with our own eyes,
Osman Bey. The carriage was empty.
They must have sensed we were coming...
...and got out of the carriage.
Then he let them in again.
With Karesi Bey's protection...
...they left our lands.
Don't...
...don't you have any shame?
Don't you have any shame?
How could you protect the infidel?
Let it be so.
Let it be so Karesi Bey.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Send envoys to the Beys.
We will gather the council. Now..
..it is time to end this.
Yes my Bey.
Karesi Bey.
Well..
Now you are free.
I wonder about something, Sofia.
You aren't messing with
Osman only for lands, I think.
This is the hatred of years
..Karesi Bey.
I won't stop until I take revenge.
Don't you..
..want Osman to die?
Tell me where you stand.
Against us?
Or beside us?
If you manage, I stand beside you.
If you fail
...I will give you one more kick when you fall.
Don't worry, Karesi Bey.
Osman will kneel sooner or later.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
-Two horses.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Well... Have a safe journey.
-Thanks, Karesi Bey.
Clear the way!
Come on, Bayhan Bey! Ride to the healing house!
Come on!
Saruca! Saruca!
My Allah..
My son... My child! What
did they do to you, son?
-Come on.
-Grab him.
Hazal Hatun.
-Come on. I got him.
-Come on.
-My son!
-Come on!
Come on!
Couldn't you save my son, husband?
My Saruca!
Hazal Hatun.
-Hazal Hatun. Hey!
-Don't do this, Hazal Hatun.
Alaaddin will take care
of him. He'll be alright.
Dastards.
-He'll be alright. -Of course he will.
He will be alright. Saruca...
Come on, Saruca -Sisters!
My son.
Alps!
Those jackal won't stop, obviously.
Increase the number of
patrols and hold the gates.
Everybody! You all keep your eyes wide open!
Only the members of this tribe will be let in.
Come on.
Orhan, what happened?
Fatma? Is everybody alright?
They're good, Holofira.
Thank Allah, they are fine.
Those heathens' plan got ruined.
Our land Sogut became their graveyard.
We sacrificed neither our
lives nor our fatherland Sogut!
Now it's time..
...to make those vile dogs...
...pay for harming our
property and making us bleed
-Allah is the greatest!
Karesiogullari Beylic
It seems Osman Bey made a great plan.
I thought he would surrender
Sogut to the heathens.
What's your dilemma, Gencer Bey?
Are you still thinking about Osman?
Never!
Osman Bey scolds me before
the other beys as if I were a kid!
Yet I joined many battles
and killed countless heathens!
I wasn't born yesterday.
I didn't deserve this, Karesi Bey.
This is the spirit.
Keep your anger alive.
Everybody will leave Osman
who never respects the morals.
My Bey is you.
I always stand with the one who
respects the morals and rules with justice.
Thank you, Gencer Bey.
Thank you.
Sancar.
Well..
Then..
...let's seal our alliance with a gift.
Thank you, Karesi Bey.
I will always keep it.
Now... Listen to me carefully.
I want you to act like one of
Osman's beys, stay with him...
...and keep me informed about everything.
Why, Karesi Bey?
To conquer Osman from the inside.
Your anger is like a mountain, Osman.
I can see that.
Karesi and his collaborators...
I will put out their fires!
Thanks, my Bala.
Thanks.
Do I have permission?
Come in, Ayse Hatun.
Osman Bey.
Yes, Ayse Hatun?
Do you have something to tell me?
I can see it.
You need to tell me something. Come here.
Come closer to me.
Come. Speak now.
My father, Ilbay has been on duty for our
state, our state and you for a long time.
And?
Are you..
..angry with me for that?
I'm not angry but proud.
He's gone for you and our land.
But Allah is my witness I miss him so much.
But I don't tell anyone.
I cry only when I'm alone in my tent.
Nobody should see me weak.
My father taught me so.
Oh... Ayse Hatun.
Your father taught you well.
Then..
Let me tell you this.
Your father will be back in the tribe soon.
Your longing will be over.
Don't be worrying.
Oh...
Fools.
How?
How could you lose her? How?
Whoever caused this will
face a worse fate than death!
Sir, Turks came to the gate
disguising as our soldiers.
And these fools opened the gate
without questioning. Is that so?
Prisoners escaped from the
dungeon before Turks came inside.
Someone killed all the guards.
-So...
There is a spy among us.
You will find him, Hristo.
You will find out who took my best leverage.
Soldiers, come with me! Now!
We'll definitely find Osman's rat, Lukas.
I will find, Sofia.
I will find and cut his breath.
Your name is Sofia, huh?
My son.
My boy. My Saruca..
My Allah..
My Allah, take from my
life and give it to my son.
I'd gladly accept that.
Don't think of the bad.
Our child will be alright.
He will be alright. Won't he, Alaaddin Bey?
I cleaned the wound well
and applied ointment on to it.
But..
Although I did my best
..he bled too much.
Molasses!
I will bring molasses! My son should drink.
Just pray for him, Hazal Hatun.
He turned out to be stronger than he looked.
He'll be alright, God willing.
God willing.
I hope he recovers.
Thank you, Alaaddin Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
May Allah be pleased with you.
My Allah..
You protected my life with your life.
Things I said to you earlier...
...are piercing my heart now.
Recover fast, Saruca.
Recover fast.
Don't leave us in sorrow.
Right before everyone
...before Fatma and all the beys, he slapped me!
He slapped me!
Calm down, Yusuf. He's the Bey.
How can I calm down?
I got disgraced before everyone!
You didn't!
You didn't, brother. He's the ruler of us.
Look.
Yusuf.
You shouldn't be angry with
the slap your Bey gives you.
You should just take a lesson.
You made a mistake. You disobeyed...
-Sister!
You don't feel disgraced
because you got slapped, Yusuf.
Just because you got slapped before Fatma Hatun
...you can't digest it.
-I can't talk to Fatma anymore.
-You will.
Yusuf.
My brother.
A man must stand up when he falls.
You made a mistake.
And you paid a heavy price.
Brother.
-Yes?
I need to tell you something.
From your eyes, I can see what you'll tell.
But you speak.
Let's see if I'm right.
Brother... So far,
we have said nothing.
We have always kept silent and
never questioned. But you see?
Begum Hatun.
She never stops making mistakes.
This isn't going well.
I know, brother.
First Karadin, then Sogut...
Wherever Begum Hatun touches, she damages us.
I know.
Well, brother... My brother
spoiled them too much.
I've been thinking about how we can
tell our Bey about this, though.
Not only her.
Her brother as well.
We trusted him for the caravan of the market.
But he couldn't protect.
Well, brother...
Why do we even need them?
He got only wounded this time.
If he dies next time, everything will be worse.
She and her brother are harming us, Cerkutay.
But how can we tell our Bey about this?
You think he can't see it?
You think we should show him?
What are we for, brother?
Why do we stand beside our Bey?
This isn't even questioning.
This is telling the truth.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Cerkutay Bey. Boran Bey.
-A meeting will be held shortly.
-Okay, Aykurt Cavus.
Okay, thanks.
Let's go.
While I thought Osman Bey
would surrender Sogut to the enemy,
...Osman Bey had other plans.
Have you ever seen Osman Bey
acting without measures, Gencer Bey?
-Attention! Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you, too.
Sit down.
We have..
...informed our enemies
once again of our morals...
...and made them understand
that even for our lives...
...we will never give up
even a piece of our land.
We fight for the Name of
The Righteous, my Bey.
We will succeed in both worlds,
with Allah's permission.
Right. Right.
We know our enemies.
Lukas on one side.
And that Hatun named Veronica on the other.
And Karesi Bey who saved...
...them from our swords on the other side.
If we are going to take lives...
...killing that Lukas dog is the
most important for me, my Bey.
Your revenge is our revenge. But...
...there is something we need to do first.
For us..
...there is a huge danger...
...and that is the snake who hides her face.
Now, tell me, what should we do...
...to make them pay for what they did?
I suggest we follow Lukas, my Bey.
After all, they are always together.
The moment they leave the
castle, we will attack them.
Gencer Bey.
Tell me, what should we
do without losing our men?
My path will require losses, my Bey.
Once they have no captives for them to hide
behind, we can go and surround Akhisar again.
Let's kill them all my Bey!
Begum Hatun...
What is your opinion?
We should do what they
did to Fatma Hatun, my Bey.
Let's disguise ourselves and confront
her at her most vulnerable moment.
What do you say, Cerkutay?
Cerkutay Bey
What do you think?
My Bey...
Whatever path..
..is most suitable for you..
..I will follow it.
And what about the others, the other suspects?
What do we know about them?
Helen has just arrived, but she is too curious.
The other one is the new groom.
Groom?
When did he come?
Our horses in the castle
were all infected by a disease.
He came around that time.
He knows a lot about horses.
Keep an eye on them. But be careful.
They must not notice. -Yes sir.
Osman is celebrating his victory now.
But..
...I will hit him at his weakest part.
Bala.
What is on your mind, Sofia?
They have increased security on
all the roads from Sogut to the tribe.
They know Veronica now as well.
You cannot go to the marketplace as well.
They will take the caravan out tomorrow.
There are difficult paths
to defend on the route.
When Bala is in Sogut, we will raid the caravan.
And when Bala hears the
news, she will fall into our trap...
...to protect the caravan.
Ah Sofia!
Your mind has no limits.
Osman will give anything for Bala, everything.
But this time, there will be no bargaining.
Only death.
First Bala, then Osman.
I will take both of their lives.
I will kill them not just
once, but a thousand times.
What's on your mind, Sofia?
Before I kill Bala..
...I will tell her such a secret that...
...she will die a thousand times.
I need to get out of here quickly and
tell that woman's name to Osman Bey.
Come on, my boy.
Are you going somewhere?
I put new horseshoes on the horses, sir.
I was going to test
them in the fields.
There's no rush.
The Turks' watchmen might be around the castle.
I'm not afraid of them sir.
-You are brave.
But you have more important
duties than riding horses in the fields.
Until tomorrow, you will
check all the horses in Akhisar.
You will identify all sick horses
that are not ready for the way.
Soldiers!
Soldiers will be with you until you are done.
They will help you.
First Baysungur and his men,
and then Fatma and the others.
My Bey, that Hatun named Veronica clearly
wants something more than our lands.
Every step she takes...
...every move she makes,
she tries to hurt us even more.
Her intention is..
..to hurt me first.
When she went to the market,
she went with her face uncovered.
But when she was facing
me, she covered her face.
She said she would only show her face to me
while killing me.
Good then.
So that she wants to kill me so much...
..let's give her a chance.
What are you thinking, Osman Bey?
Karesi Bey..
...wanted to turn these
lands into a hunting ground.
He wanted to hunt infidels together.
Two faced Karesi Bey.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Send news to Karesi Bey.
I am...
...inviting him to my hunt.
Yes my Bey.
Now Karesi Bey...
..will do his best to secure..
..his alliance with infidels.
First, he will mention
about the hunt to his friends.
What do you want to
achieve with this plan, my Bey?
Now our goal will be this.
When he tells his allies about the hunting
place, they will think we will fall into a trap.
Veronica will come there.
Then Veronica will be in our hands.
Boran, Cerkutay.
Tomorrow, at Gundogan...
...you will go to the places
we will hunt and set the traps.
But you will take all the precautions.
Yes my Bey.
You can leave.
What happened, Beys?
Do you have something to say?
My Bey...
We are not sure if we will
have gone too far, but...
...there's an issue that makes us concerned.
My Bey, we...
...couldn't say that at the council but...
-You had to!
If this is about the council..
You had to speak...
...when I gave you the chance.
The council is over.
Now it's time to hunt.
Now..
Go and do your duties.
-Yes my Bey.
You called me Bala Hatun.
You came together with your
brother, right, Begum Hatun?
Yes, thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Osman Bey, Sogut
and our children are saved.
Good.
Now it is time to answer.
I know I cannot make up for my mistake.
Knowing it does not change anything, Begum.
There is no compensation for this mistake.
Do you allow people to trade in our
marketplace without questioning them?
Didn't you investigate before
letting that devil into the market?
I did, of course, Bala Hatun.
But no one knew her.
I sent Alps around and I was
waiting for them to inform me.
No one knew her.
While you were waiting for news...
..that devil abducted my child, Begum!
From the marketplace you were
watching over and protecting.
Am I the only one at fault, Bala
Hatun? My brother was also..
Shut up!
Don't look for someone else
to blame for your mistake.
You let that devil into the marketplace.
And you will pay the price.
If I have to pay a price, I will.
We gave you a duty to make up for your mistake.
And you failed that as well.
But I will talk to Osman Bey.
I will dismiss you.
Know that.
Gunkurt.
My Bey.
Take this to Karesi without letting them notice.
Yes my Bey.
Learning Osman's move
will be very useful for Karesi.
Osman.
Ah Osman.
If it wasn't for my love for you...
...I would set this tribe on fire..
...and show that Bala her place.
But...
..you don't see me..
..and you don't see my love.
Like the dagger I've carried for years,
the love I've carried with forty locks.
My Allah..
If giving up was possible...
But no...
I can't..
Giving up on my love...
...is giving up on my life!
Bala...
Despite you..
I won't give up on Osman.
Gonca.
Are you alright? What happened?
Aunt, you seem pale.
Did you receive bad news?
No, no my Fatma. I am alright.
What are you doing here?
I was telling my brother how I escaped.
Brother...
Alright. Alright. Tell her.
-Do you want me to tell you as well?
-Yes my Fatma.
We ran away and then..
...they saved us...
...they said "Wear the clothes
of Byzantium soldiers"...
...then we fought and
killed them with our swords...
That woman has a problem with us.
So, she won't stop.
My Bala, everyone in the tribe will be cautious.
You too.
But most importantly, my Fatma.
Don't worry, my Bey.
I will take care of it.
I will give Fatma a duty in the tribe.
Okay, okay, okay.
We must also please the people of Sogut.
Orhan, this task is yours, my son.
-Yes my Bey.
I will think about what needs
to be done for the people.
Actually...
The goods that we keep in the storehouse,
which Karesi Bey wanted to take from us...
Can't we trade them in the Sogut market?
It will increase the trade,
and the people will be happy.
You've thought well, my daughter.
She thought well, my Bala.
Then, this duty is yours.
Mine.
So, where is Alaeddin? Where is my Fatma?
My Bey, Fatma took Alaeddin and Gonca captive.
They will come soon.
-Yes?
-That's right.
I put the sword in and ran away.
Alright, sister.
Alright, dear sister.
You told me three times.
I really got it.
Hey, don't be so impatient.
My daughter, come here. Come.
Tell me about it.
Don't do this, father.
She's been telling the same story for an hour.
Stop talking.
You keep quiet.
What happened there, daughter?
Father.
My brothers envy me.
That's why they are doing this.
I proved myself.
-I can join the battles, right?
-No battles for you.
Why would you?
You will just sit by me.
You will always stick with us.
No more going to the market place either.
-Mother.
No battles!
Father.
Mother.
Speaking of the market...
Gonca has an idea.
Right. My sister-in-saw has
a great idea. Tell them, sister.
No battles. You speak, my girl.
Father, what about putting the
goods in the store in the market?
You see how hard your
daughter-in-laws work, Osman Bey?
My dear, Holofira just said the same thing.
We assigned her.
Well..
You tell me, dear.
How did you escape from the carriage?
Oh no, my Bey.
Don't do this, father.
Are you still talking? Tell me, dear.
Father.
-Well...
-Hmm..
Karesiogullari Beylic
Osman Bey invites us to the hunt tomorrow, huh?
Sancar.
He's up to something, but...
Osman Bey can't make a plan against you, my Bey.
If he does, he'll be the one to be hunted.
The wolf sees the lion as a
prey not because he's brave...
..but because he's blind.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in, Kanyumaz.
My Bey, I've brought a note from Gencer Bey.
Osman Bey knows that Lukas and the
woman with him escaped with your help.
And he thinks you will let them
know about his invitation for you.
While they attempt to kill Osman Bey
when he's unprotected during the hunt
...Osman Bey will hunt them.
Osman.
You think you are smart.
But I'm always a step ahead of you.
-Sancar.
-Yes, my Bey?
Inform Osman Bey...
...that I'm accepting his invitation.
As you order, my Bey.
Bala, just spill the beans.
Begum Hatun, my Bey.
She made many mistakes in
Karadin and we forgave her.
She acted impertinently and we tolerated.
We gave her a duty in the marketplace of
Sogut because she had weak ties with us.
But she failed.
We've seen what her failure cost.
Of course.
I'm thinking about a suitable
punishment for her failure.
I don't want to
punish her, but...
...someone good should take over her duty.
I think we should dismiss Begum Hatun, my Bey.
Do you have someone in your mind?
Yes.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Begum Hatun is
here. She wants to see you.
Let her in.
Speak, Begum Hatun.
As you came at this hour, you must
have something important to say, huh?
Yes.
Osman Bey.
First, I want you to know that I'm loyal
to you and your cause until my last day.
My loyalty will never end.
Thank you, Begum Hatun.
But..
I made a mistake during the
kidnapping of Fatma Hatun.
With your permission
...I'd like to be dismissed
from my duty on the market.
And I want no other duties
but having conquests with you.
You will keep your duty on the market.
I'm not dismissing you.
Don't ask me for any other duties...
...or dismissal from your current duty.
You may leave.
Whatever you order, Osman Bey.
You don't want to dismiss her, my Bey.
So you must have a plan, huh?
This is a duty of the state.
Nobody can change it at their wills.
Look.
You got worried for nothing.
You pulled your beautiful
face for nothing, Holofira.
I'm trying to stay strong.
But I can't help it, Orhan.
I got scared.
Fatma told me..
The arrow almost...
-The arrow...
..hit the talisman, Holofira.
It hit the talisman you put around my neck.
Look. I didn't get
wounded at all.
But the talisman... It got destroyed.
Never mind. It protected you.
Allah protected me, Holofira.
He protected me through you and this talisman.
Let's see what's written inside.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
“Allah alone is sufficient as an aid for us and
He is the best Protector.” [Al Imran Surah 173]
What does that mean?
It's written in an Qur'an.
It means..
Allah alone is sufficient as an aid for us...
...and He is the best Protector.
Beautiful.
My Holofira.
I will win this time, Osman.
Sorry, Bala.
But you will fall behind. I will win.
You say so?
Yes.
Hey, don't look at me
like this. You are cheating.
Not cheating but loving you, my Osman.
Come on, Alaca!
Well... Come on, Iltutan
You cheated, Bala. But I will
show you what my love means.
It's my love, Osman!
Bala!
My Bala..
Bala.
-Are you alright?
-I'm fine, Osman.
Bala?
Osman.
Bala.
Bala!
My Bala.
Osman.
Bala? Bala!
Bala. Bala.
My Bala, you will be alright.
-You'll be alright.
-Osman.
My Dark Osman.
My love...
-I'll tell you something.
-Go ahead.
Go ahead.
Speak, my Bala.
-What did we say?
The one who loves the most runs faster.
Yes. Don't worry. We will run together again.
We will run together again.
Bala, hold on.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah
...and I bear witness that
Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah.
Bala. Bala..
Bala.
My Allah.
May You let it be a good sign.
May Allah's mercy and blessings be upon you.
My Allah.
You're the One Who protects, my Allah.
You're the One Who forgives.
Even if I never stopped
worshiping You in this world
...my gratitude could never
be enough for Your gifts.
I know that.
You gave me my state, my people, my family,
...my love in this world, my wife.
You gave me my Bala.
My Allah.
If Bala weren't in this world
..colors would fade away.
And all the sounds would go silent.
Don't let me lose Bala.
Don't test me with this, my Allah.
Please let both of us..
...walk together in this
path until our last day.
Halime.
My Halime.
Bala..
Kayi Tents
My Alaeddin.
My Gonca.
You've been looking bad since yesterday.
Did something happen? Tell me.
There is something but...
I don't know how to say it, Alaeddin.
Come.
My Gonca.
Are you sad because the
duty was given to Holofira?
Yes. Right.
My mother wants Hatuns
to get along with Holofira.
And she is doing the right thing.
But..
...she sometimes forgets about me...
Look..
How can someone forget you, Hatun?
They can't, right.
Sure not.
My mother is just, my rose.
I know.
My mother thinks of all of us.
-Right. Right.
But..
I know how to make you smile.
How?
Alaeddin..
Yes... Right, my rose.
May your beautiful face always smile, my Gonca.
Look, this will help you and your nerves.
Right, Trickster Hatun?
Yes, Scholar, yes.
Now I am leaving.
May Allah protect you.
May Allah protect you too, my Bey.
Alright.
Let's go.
How am I going to tell this to you, Alaeddin?
Karesiogullari Beylic
Why did you call us here in a rush, Karesi Bey?
There is important news.
Osman Bey is inviting me for a hunt.
Hunt means union.
Will you..
...make an alliance with Osman?
If I was going to do that...
...you would not be standing before me.
Osman is calling me for a
hunt, but you are the prey, Hatun.
What does that mean, Karesi Bey?
Osman will organize a hunt with me
today and make himself seem like a prey...
...and you will lose your lives
as you are trying to kill him.
I will not fall into this trap.
Karesi Bey.
If I hadn't told you..
...Osman would've done
all those things to you...
We will go and hunt today.
You will decide the rest.
Attention! Osman Bey.
I hope you return with the good
news of your vengeance, my Bey.
May your hunt be blessed
God willing my Bala, God willing.
It's time to send those
who threaten our people
and our state seven
layers beneath the earth.
May your market be prosperous, Bala.
Bring the horses.
The hunting time has come.
Come on sisters.
Come on, we are going to Sogut!
Come on Alps!
Come on brothers!
We will set the traps as
quickly as possible, come on!
Yes my Bey.
Brother..
Do you think we angered our Bey too much?
Brother, we didn't know what to say before
our Bey because we were mad at Begum Hatun.
Exactly.
We didn't. And he told
us that. And he was right.
But I wish we could tell him about our problems.
Brother, once this hunting
is over, we will speak.
Come on Alps!
The direction of the
enemy's arrival, the direction
of their escape, and every
path will have a trap set.
-Come on lions! Come on!
-Yes my Bey.
Are the preparations completed?
My Bey, as you ordered, our Alps
are setting traps all around the forest.
It will be completed
soon, God willing.
This area on the hill...
When I meet with Karesi, that will
be the best place for them to strike me.
As you said, we've placed the
most secret traps near that location.
Traps are good.
But what if she does not fall into the trap?
My Bey, we saw the Hatun.
Her mind works like a devil's.
We need to take other precautions.
My brother is right.
If she doesn't fall into
the trap when she comes...
...your life will be in danger, my Bey.
For this reason, the traps need to be
set on the paths as soon as possible.
You're right.
But no matter how much a hunter knows tricks,
the prey will always find a way. Boran.
My bey.
You will prepare all the traps.
-That woman will never pass through here.
-Yes, my Bey.
The spear won't fit in the sack now.
A storm will break out here today.
But they will be the ones who die. Come on.
Gonca.
You have more effort
than her in the marketplace.
Bala is not being fair to you.
Open your eyes.
Whatever my mother does..
...she does it to fix the relations between
Holofira and Kayi Hatuns, Begum Hatun.
If you keep justifying them like
this, you will be left here like this.
Doesn't it upset you, Gonca?
It surely upsets me.
They ignore me.
But what can I do? There's nothing I can do.
Sometimes..
...we must know our places...
...and accept our fates, Begum Hatun.
Even if you accept it...
..I won't allow this treatment
and injustice towards you.
Osman prepared his own end with his game.
He put his head in front of my sword.
Everything is ready, Sofia, but
you know Osman better than I do.
What if you fall into his trap?
Osman is in my hands.
They are too blind to see the
death that is approaching them.
You say we will be the hell of Kayis.
-Yes.
I've waited for years for revenge, Lukas.
I lived for today.
I won't stop you from hunting him, Sofia.
Today, those goat herders will
become a wounded and helpless herd.
Commander Lukas.
The disease in Akhisar may
have affected these horses as well.
Just in case, you...
-There is no need.
Pray that these horses are not sick.
Otherwise, you'll die
under the nails of my horse.
Osman Bey will learn your name.
But first, let me go after you
and see what you're planning.
Gonca Hatun.
Since Holofira Hatun will
sell goods in the marketplace...
...you should take care of the caravan.
You choose the goods
that will come to the caravan.
If my mother allows, I'll do it, Begum Hatun.
Begum Hatun.
I gave the duty to Holofira.
It's not a problem for me, mother Bala.
Come for a second.
What are you trying to do?
Are you giving orders against my orders?
Bala Hatun.
I thought I was controlling the marketplace.
If I can't decide who will take care
of the caravans, then why am I here?
Your problem is not with the caravan, Begum.
Of course not.
Gonca is very upset.
And I brought justice.
-Are you questioning my justice Begum?
-Not at all.
I am just doing my duty.
Gonca knows the marketplace better.
Mother..
If it's going to be a
problem, I won't take the task.
Begum Hatun..
-...just thought I...
Is there a need for her to think of you, Gonca?
There is, that's why I do, Bala Hatun.
As the person responsible for the market, I
can only entrust such a big trade to Gonca.
If you say I don't have
the authority to do so...
...then I am asking you to dismiss me.
What are we going to do Bala mother?
Shall we split the goods in two?
Holofira, you are responsible for the
goods that will be sold in the marketplace.
Gonca, you will take care of the
goods to be prepared for the caravan.
Yes mother.
My Bey.
Karesi Bey is coming.
Let him come
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you, too.
Peace be upon you, too.
Karesi Bey.
Come. Come.
Take a seat here.
Thank you.
You surprised me...
...with your invitation a lot, Osman Bey.
You wanted to join the council of beys,
...discuss with us and go to the hunt.
You are elder than us.
So I wanted to listen to my elder.
I wanted to make your wishes come true today.
Thank you.
Those who respect elders shall be
happy in this world and the afterlife
..our ancestors said.
May you be happy.
Thank you.
In these frontiers..
...where we had many battles
and defeated countless heathens
...you and I are different sides.
We... Both of us...
...fight for our cause in Allah's path.
We have the same destination and the same cause.
So tell me.
Why are our ways separate?
Have you every thought?
I have.
Nafs(self), Osman Bey.
Although the intentions are good,
...nafs (self) says it wants to lead the way.
Well... It's the fruit of
the ambition inside us...
...which makes our sides different.
Yes, nafs (self).
Nafs (self).
Well..
It's a trap if you get overwhelmed by it.
But if you can beat your nafs (self)...
...it's a great weapon.
So you say I'm one of
those who fall into the trap.
And you are one of those who hold the weapon.
-Is that so, Osman Bey?
-Karesi Bey.
I'm a hunter here.
But why do you think you're
the prey to fall into the trap?
I'm neither a hunter nor a prey, Osman Bey.
I'm a high plane tree whose
shadow both of them run under.
You say so?
Thank you.
Come on then. Well..
Let's hunt under your shadow.
Here we go.
-After you.
-Alright.
Come on, alps.
Have a safe journey.
You thought well about
selling these goods in Sogut.
Sogut got s thanks to you.
We all got lifeful, Ulgen.
Hatuns, thanks for your efforts.
Stalls look wonderful.
Thanks to you, Holofira Hatun.
It happened thanks to all of you.
Listen. If you stand strong like this,
...they'll get used to you
quickly. That's what they do.
They like pushing the new bride.
You say so?
Come on. Gonca!
I said Gonca.
-What's the matter?
-I'm so confused, Ulgen.
Well..
I need to talk to my mother.
We're under attack!
He's running off! Catch him!
When you draw the bow
...do you ever think "what if I'm
the prey at the point of the arrow"?
The dog who doesn't walk well...
..will draw wolves to the herd.
I fell among the dogs at times.
I sometimes became the prey while hunting.
But I'm still a wolf.
And I can beat a thousand
of dogs when it's time.
They're about to come here.
My Bey.
Our scouts have sent a message.
-They're coming from that way.
-Who is coming?
Hunters, Karesi Bey.
Don't worry.
Nobody will hurt you.
I'm the prey at the point of the arrow.
And you're a high plane tree
whose shadow we will run under.
Come on.
How can I tell my mother
about this? Oh Begum Hatun...
What have you done?
Well..
I can't help it.
I have to tell my mother.
They attacked the caravan!
Mother.
Yes, dear.
I need to talk to you about an urgent matter.
What is it?
Mother.
-I am...
Bala Hatun. Bala Hatun.
-The caravan. It got attacked.
-What?
Attacked? Prepare the horses
immediately. We're leaving!
Do you feel the blood smell on the air, Hristo?
Shortly, this place will be
stained with Turkish blood.
Place the soldiers behind the trees.
I'll start avenging Arkadius and
all our brothers with Bala Hatun.
Hide the horses!
Get behind the trees!
Bala will be here soon.
Bala Hatun?
Oh no.
Come on, hurry up.
Osman's rat is you, huh?
I know who you are!
Stableman.
You'll never be able to inform Osman.
While you see just one
...Osman Bey sees a thousand.
You'll be destroyed with your plans, Lukas.
Stableman.
Soldiers!
What now?
He can't live long with that wound.
We will wait for Bala.
My Bey, arrow!
You snake!
We're drawing back!
Come on, alps!
We'll draw them here to
the smoke. Aykurt, burn it!
As you order, my Bey.
Let's go.
They are over here!
Sons. Boran, Cerkutay.
You come with me.
The rest will split up.
Let them come.
Come on!
Boran, Cerkutay. Move!
Now!
Come on, Boran.
Catch him!
You two, go that way. You come with me!
Not now.
Not now. Come on!
My Allah, give me strength.
Give me strength.
I have to inform Osman Bey.
He must have gone this way.
Hurry up. Let's catch that traitor!
Hold on, Ilbay. Hold on.
Split up. Split up.
Come here.
You all come.
Wait for a second.
Come here, demon.
Come to me.
Come here.
You said you'd show your face
only when you killed me, huh?
Whoever attempts to mess
with my nation and state...
...has no rights to see the daylight or breathe.
Come here.
My Bey, that's not her.
This isn't the hatun who abducted us.
What?
How come?
Why are they so late?
Didn't they get the news about the attack?
Sofia.
They're coming.
Bala and her daughter-in-laws.
Osman? What about Osman?
He thinks he hunted me down.
When he takes off the
mask, he'll see he is the prey.
I'd love to see that moment.
I'm the hunter today, Lukas.
Today will be Osman's darkest day.
Bala, Holofira, Gonca... I will kill them all.
My Allah, give me strength.
I'm coming, my Bey.
I'm coming.
She has sent another one instead, huh?
She knew we prepared a trap for her.
She deceived us.
Well..
How did that snake woman
know we made a plan for her?
Karesi Bey!
I knew you'd bring the heathens here.
But how did you learn about my plan?
Obviously,
..there is a spy among us!
You invited me to the hunt and I joined.
I don't know about the rest.
Where is your respect again?
You blame me again!
Here is the respect!
Karesi Bey.
Now tell me.
Who told you about the plan?
My Bey!
My Bey. -Ilbay.
He is injured. -Alaeddin..
Come.
Karesi Bey...
My Bey. -What happened to you?
-My Bey, Lukas... Lukas, my Bey...
He made a treacherous plan...
..with a woman named Sofia.
Who?
Sofia.
Osman.
This might be the last time
you are seeing your daughter.
Sofia?
Didn't you kill that Hatun named Sofia...
...years ago?
Sofia..
My Bey, how is this possible?
My Bey... My Bey... They will..
...lure Bala Hatun to a trap in Karacam.
It's..
..it's that snake!
But Karacam is very far from here, my Bey!
Mother..
My mother's life is in danger, father!
My mother is in danger! -Sofia!
Alps, to the horses! Turan!
Take Ilbay to the tribe.
Be careful.
Check the Alps.
What happened here?
Welcome to your funeral, Bala.
You snake.
You played a game, huh?
Show me your face, you coward!
Don't worry.
You will see my face today Bala.
Kill them all!
No one will survive here!
Attack!
Begum!
I will kill you with my own hands!
I am your angel of death.
You will die today, Bala.
Before you die, I will give
you such a secret that...
...you will beg me to live.
Bala.
Osman.
Goodbye Bala.
Bala.
I see that you are really happy today Sofia.
I've waited so long for this day Lukas.
So long.
Be careful.
Check the Alps, come on!
What happened here?
Brother..
Come on.
Welcome, Bala!
Trap
Be careful, be careful.
We were not done.
Devil..
You attempted to hurt my daughter,
I will kill you with my own hands!
Aren't you going to ask what
happened to Osman, Bala?
He was going to hunt me, right?
Osman.
How do you know that?
I know everything, Bala.
I wish you could die with Osman but...
I will kill you today.
Those are courageous words...
...for a scared woman, you devil!
Scared woman? -Right!
You are scared, since you
are hiding your face! But today...
..you will see hell.
When you find out who I am..
...you will be really surprised, Bala.
-Show me then!
Attack!
I will take my brother's revenge!
Unfortunately, you won't live that long, Begum.
Show me your face!
Surprise me as you said!
Sofia.
How did you..
I did not die, Bala.
But you will die today.
Sofia..
I've waited for today for so long, Bala...
I took an oath to be your
Azrael. Before you die...
...I will...
...give you such a secret that...
You will beg me to live!
That will never happen Sofia!
Never.
Sofia.